Denise Weber

(330) 212-1204 dweber0001@gmail.com

Personal Summary

I am making a career change after working in the medical records field for many years. Due to offshoring, my entire QIS team was laid off 11/1/2018, and I was given the opportunity to obtain an associate degree in software development, which I pursued wholeheartedly! I am now seeking a new career in which I can integrate my prior work experience with the developer skills I have obtained, and am looking forward to joining a great company that I can contribute to, learn from, and grow with. Additional skills I bring: Independent learner, long-term remote worker, positive/empathetic and optimistic attitude, strong multitasking/time-management and communication skills, diligent problem solver, passionate about learning, training, growing and technology.

Work Experience

Quality Improvement Specialist (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

October 2008 to November 2018

Duties: Drive Service Delivery excellence for assigned clients via compliance with Quality Program standards utilizing live audits and positive feedback. Perform monthly assigned quality audits for clients (proofreading/editing/scoring). Due to offshoring, my entire team was laid off November 2018.

Manager, Service Delivery (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

July 2007 to October 2008

Managed 5 Supervisors and staff of MTs and QA staff. Daily Goals: Trained/Supported Supervisors to achieve workflow and quality goals, address stat issues. Hiring, training, PMP/PIP, termination. Responsibilities: Performance of Supervisors, MTs and QA staff in attaining TATs, quality, and customer service goals for the 105 hospitals/clinics in our book of business. **Company restructure 10/2008:** Elimination of all Manager Roles; I was retained in the Quality Improvement Specialist role.

QA Manager/Audit Supervisor (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

July 2003 to July 2007

Managed 32 FTE QA Specialists. Developed QA plan to address quality issues/TAT and increase QA production. **Promoted 06/2006: Audit Supervisor** N Region as part of new national team. Duties: interview, hire, train team of 15 auditors. Lotus Notes Audit DB administrator. Developed training materials, led webinars, trained new auditors, liaison for database users. **Promoted to Manager, SD.**

Education

Associate Degree - Software Development

Sinclair Community College - Dayton, OH

April 2019 to December 2020

Graduated with Honors. Cumulative GPA of 3.41

Certificates: • IT Fundamentals 08/2020 • Fast Track Programming 12/2020

Links

Portfolio: https://dweber0001.github.io/
Github.com/dweber0001

Skills

- ASP.NET (1 year)
- CSS (2 years)
- NodeJS
- FLASK/JINJA2
- GITHUB

- BOOTSTRAP
- HTML5 (2 years)
- NPM
- HEROKU
- ORACLE SQL

- C# (1 year)
- JAVASCRIPT (1 year)
- ReactJS (< 1 year)
- MongoDB
- DATABASE DESIGN ERD

Additional Skills

- Medical terminology, proofreading, editing, auditing, and reporting. (10+ years)
- Team building, coaching, leading virtual teams, training, communication, assessing performance, managing performance issues, PMP/PIP, hiring, setting goals. (5 years)
- MS Office products, research/analysis, small business accounting, QuickBooks.